<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Quantum Protocol Zoo&#39;s Repository</title>
    <link>https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Quantum Protocol Zoo&#39;s Repository</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 06:51:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Protocol Repository</title>
      <link>https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/protocol-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 06:51:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/protocol-repo/</guid>
      <description>Release 0.1 for the protocol repository In addition to the Quantum Protocol Zoo hosted at https://wiki.veriqloud.fr we have started implementing some of the protocols using simulaQron and CQC. This repository is hosted at github https://github.com/quantumprotocolzoo/protocols.
It already contains a few protocols. More will be added in the future. We also plan to increase the robustness of these implementations and their functionality, ultimately giving access to a protocol library to be used in more complex situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizations</title>
      <link>https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/visualizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 16:57:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/visualizations/</guid>
      <description>What can I do with my resources ? When new physical capacbilities are built, new protocols are de facto available for implementations. To discover protocols and functionalities availables for a given set of resources, follow this link to activate the &amp;ldquo;Resources Visualization&amp;rdquo;. Click on the nodes to select which nodes are available to you. Protocols will be highlighted when they can be implemented using the selected resources.
Which resources do I need ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Protocol Zoo&#39;s Repository</title>
      <link>https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/qpz-repo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quantumprotocolzoo.github.io/posts/qpz-repo/</guid>
      <description>What will you find here? The Quantum Protocol Zoo aims at providing an oerview of selected quantum communication protocols arranged into functionalities, protocols per se and resources needed to implement them.
This repo is tightly integrated with the zoo as it contains simulaQron code for implementing these protocols using quantum optics devices or simulators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>